完了 完了
The end.
这是个很悲哀的故事
That was a very sad story.
这里面有寓意 这里面有寓意
Aye, and there's a moral to it.
是的 很好的寓意
Oh, yes, a very good moral
-如果你是一只牡蛎  -这是一次很好的访问
-if you happen to be an oyster. -Well, it's been a very nice visit
我们再朗诵一首诗
Another recitation.
抱歉 不过… 名字叫“威廉父亲”
- I'm sorry, but-- - Entitled ''Father William.'' - But really, I'm--
第一段
First verse.
您老了 威廉父亲 年轻人说
You are old, Father William the young man said
您的头发全变白了
And your hair has become very white
但您还是在不断地倒立
And yet you incessantly stand on your head
你觉得您这样的年纪合适吗？
Do you think at your age it is right, it's right Do you think at your age it is right
“在我年轻的时候” 威廉的父亲回答说
Well, in me youth Father William replied to his son